Guide to the Apple Computer, Inc. Records M1007
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Audiovisual materials, Series 14
  - 3rd Party videotapes, Subseries 14.2
    - McKenna, Regis. TV pitch, undated; 1 videocassette of 1 (Umatic) (7:10 min.): sd., col.; 3/4 in. (Box 25, Videotape 3)
    - Peat Marwick. Four slide xfer w/WTC, 1984 Nov. 26; 109; 1 videocassette of 1 (Umatic) (5 min.): sd., col.; 3/4 in. (Box 25, Videotape 4)
      High tech module
    - Pepsi Cola Co. Various, undated; 76; 1 videocassette of 1 (Umatic): sd., col.; 3/4 in. (Box 25, Videotape 5)
      Best of Pepsi (4:30 min.) -- Pepl-1026 Ann Mach (1 min.) -- L and S (0:30 min.) -- Chimpanzee Cole response (0:30 min.) -- 5% fewer calories: McAllister shopper (0:30 min.) -- Thank Houston: Taste that won Texas (0:30) -- Redneck (lizard) (0:30 min.) -- Bill Cosby: bacon/cheeseburger (0:30 min.) -- Taste superiority: bottle opening (0:30 min.) -- Dancing bottles (0:30 min.) -- Compact six: revised (0:30 min.) -- Vanishing bottles (0:30 min.) -- Cmaping revised (0:30 min.) -- Sailing revised (0:30 min.)
    - Phone slave: English & Japanese version, 1984 May 24; 1 videocassette of 1 (Umatic): sd., col.; 3/4 in. (Box 25, Videotape 6)
      Negroponte, Nicholas
    - , undated; 1 videocassette of 1 (Umatic): sd., col.; 3/4 in. (Box 26, Videotape 3)
  - John Sculley interviews, speeches, and appearances, Subseries 14.3
    This subseries includes videotapes of interviews, speeches, guest appearances and other public appearances by John Sculley during his tenure as CEO of Apple Computer.
    - American Society of Mechanical Engineers award: John Sculley, 1987 July 22; 173; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 26, Videotape 1)
    - Apple Communications Meeting. Open Apple: interview with John Sculley, Jay Elliot, and Steve Wozniak, 1986 Apr. 30; 139; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (cy 1) (Box 26, Videotape 2)
    - Apple Communications Meeting. Open Apple: interview with John Sculley, Jay Elliot, and Steve Wozniak, 1986 Apr. 30; 140; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (cy 2) (Box 26, Videotape 3)
    - Apple Computer: John Sculley, 1990 Mar. 23; 1 videocassette of 1 (Beta): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 26, Videotape 4)
    - Boeing Industry Awareness Dinner with John Sculley, 1991 Jan. 23; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 26, Videotape 5)
    - Brown University. In the information age: a conversation with Thomas J. Watson, Jr., John Sculley III, Frederick A. Wang, undated; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (65 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 26, Videotape 6)
    - CBS This morning., 1988 Nov. 11; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 26, Videotape 7)
      Interview with John Sculley
    - CBS This morning. At home with - John Sculley, [1989 Nov. 17]; 1 videocassette of 1 (Beta): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 26, Videotape 8)
    - CBS This morning. At home with - John Sculley, 1989 Nov. 17; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 26, Videotape 9)
    - CEO spotlight, 1988 Dec. 5; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 26, Videotape 10)
    - The Computer show, 1987 Oct. 27; 178; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (58:50 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (cy 1) (Box 27, Videotape 1)
      John Sculley / Apple Computer -- Matt McConnell / Compatible Systems
    - The Computer show, 1987 Oct. 27; 179; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (58:50 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (cy 2) (Box 27, Videotape 2)
    - Comshare 1990 users conference, 179; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 27, Videotape 3)
      Keynote presentation / John Sculley, Apple Computer, Inc. -- President's address / Richard Crandall, Comshare, Inc.
    - DuPont. Last take, 1988 Sept. 12; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 27, Videotape 4)
    - Effective mathematics teaching: Genise, 1986 June 17; 145; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (16 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 27, Videotape 5)
      John Sculley with math whiz kids
    - Emerging issues: John Sculley, Apple Computer, 1989 Feb. 1; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (28:30 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 27, Videotape 6)
    - FNN Aircheck, 1987 Oct. 27; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 27, Videotape 7)
    - FNN Evening news, 1988 May 27; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (3:01): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 27, Videotape 8)
      Malcolm Forbes comments on John Sculley on CEO spotlight
    - FNN Masters of the decade: John Sculley, Apple Computer, undated; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 27, Videotape 9)
    - H & Q: Apple Computer, John Sculley, President & CEO, 1986 May 12; 142; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 27, Videotape 10)
    - Intermedia, Inc. Risktaking: the essence of growth, 1992 July; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 28, Videotape 1)
    - Interview with John Sculley, President, Apple Computer, Inc., 1987 Jan. 13; 164; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 28, Videotape 2)
    - John Sculley: 2.5 million [Japanese production], undated; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 28, Videotape 3)
    - John Sculley: a statement of direction, 1985 June 25; 144; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (21:38 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 28, Videotape 4)
    - John Sculley: a statement of direction, 1985 June 26; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (22 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 28, Videotape 5)
    - John Sculley "ad age" reel, 1985 Aug. 17; 122; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (5:52 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 28, Videotape 6)
    - John Sculley: AppleWorld 87, 1987; 193; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (cy 1) (Box 28, Videotape 7)
    - John Sculley: AppleWorld 87, 1987; 194; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (cy 2) (Box 28, Videotape 8)
    - John Sculley, CEO Apple Computer Inc., presentation at Owen [Vanderbilt], 1988 Dec. 1; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 28, Videotape 9)
    - John Sculley compilation: Girato Cass N 5 (2 parte) 1a-2a-1b-2b, 1992 July 29; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (120 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 28, Videotape 10)
    - John Sculley compilation: Girato Cass N 5 (2 parte) 3b-4b-5b, 1992 July 29; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (120 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 29, Videotape 1)
    - John Sculley compilation: Inglese/Girato Cass N 1-2-3-4-5 printa parte, 1992 July 29; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (120 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 29, Videotape 2)
    - John Sculley lecture, Flint Center, undated; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (70 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 29, Videotape 3)
      Part 1 (58 min.) -- Part 2 (12 min.)
    - John Sculley N.M.S., 1986 Oct.; 155; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (70 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (cy 1) (Box 29, Videotape 4)
    - John Sculley N.M.S., 1986 Oct.; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (70 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (cy 2) (Box 29, Videotape 5)
    - John Sculley - news clips, 1984 Apr.; 95; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (25:50 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 29, Videotape 6)
      News clips featuring Apple (18:40 min.) -- John Sculley TV pitch - Regis McKenna (7:10 min.)
    - John Sculley satellite conference. Take 4, 1988 Sept. 12; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 29, Videotape 7)
    - John Sculley Uniform presentation, undated; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 29, Videotape 8)
    - John Sculley & Bernie G. on education. -- Unedited version, 1990 Apr. 9; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (30 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 29, Videotape 9)
    - John Sculley's roast Stewart Alsop, 1990 Jan. 26; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (3:25 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 29, Videotape 10)
    - John's speech, undated; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 30, Videotape 1)
    - Macintosh momentum: developing in the 90's / John Sculley. -- [Cupertino, Calif.]: Apple TV, 1991. Note: speech at the Software Publishers Association Spring Symposium, 1991 Mar. 18; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 30, Videotape 2)
    - MacWorld expo, Boston, Mass. / producer Robert Zakon, 1987; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 30, Videotape 3)
      Speech by John Sculley
    - MacWorld '91: Sculley speech, 1991; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (60 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (cy 1) (Box 30, Videotape 4)
    - MacWorld '91: Sculley speech, 1991; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (60 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (cy 2) (Box 30, Videotape 5)
    - Matt Powers [beer bash], undated; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 30, Videotape 6)
      John Sculley at Matt Powers beer bash
    - Nation's Business Today. CEO closeup: John Sculley, Apple Computer, undated; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 30, Videotape 7)
    - Nation's Business Today. Excerpts from Naisbitt & Com. interview with John Sculley, undated; 49; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (cy 1) (Box 30, Videotape 8)
    - Nation's Business Today. Excerpts from Naisbitt & Com. interview with John Sculley, undated; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (cy 2) (Box 30, Videotape 9)
    - NBC News. Excerpts, 1992 Jan. 10; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 30, Videotape 10)
      NBC Nightly News segment on U.S./Japan competition mentioning Apple Computer (1992 Jan. 7) -- NBC Morning News interview with John Sculley (1992 Jan. 10)
    - PBS-TV. American interests: John Sculley, 1992 Feb. 15; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 31, Videotape 1)
    - Pinnacle. John Sculley of Apple Computer / CNN TV Network, 1988 May 28; 240; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (30 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 31, Videotape 2)
    - Sculley presentation at Stanford, 1984 Feb. 7; 90; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 31, Videotape 3)
    - SkyTel Corp. John Sculley, undated; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 31, Videotape 4)
    - Uomini e affari. John Sculley, 1989 Apr. 19; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (10 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 31, Videotape 5)
    - WWMM [World Wide Management Meeting?] - Sculley presents Spindler with 10 year pin, undated; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 31, Videotape 6)
    - Apple Computer. John Sculley: satellite conference. Take 4, 1988 Sept. 12; 1 videocassette of 1 (Mini U-matic): sd., col.; 3/4 in. (Box 33, Videotape 1)
    - Apple Computer. John Sculley: DuPont. Last Take, 1988 Sept. 12; 1 videocassette of 1 (Mini U-matic): sd., col.; 3/4 in. (Box 33, Videotape 2)
    - Interview with John Sculley on ITV Television, UK, undated; 1 videocassette of 1 (U-matic): sd., col.; 3/4 in. (Box 33, Videotape 3)
    - John Sculley compilation, 1988 Sept. 19; 1 videocassette of 1 (U-matic): sd., col.; 3/4 in. (Box 33, Videotape 4)
      1984 -- Going to work -- War room -- Knowledge navigator
    - John Sculley Digital World, undated; 1 videocassette of 1 (U-matic): sd., col.; 3/4 in. (Box 33, Videotape 5)
      Map of Chicago / Random House -- Newstream / Motorola -- Paris map / Human Interface
    - John Sculley keynote address, 1988 Jan. 15; 202; 1 videocassette of 1 (U-matic) (ca. 38 min.): sd., col.; 3/4 in. (Box 33, Videotape 6)
    - John Sculley live satellite feed, 1986 Apr. 21; 133; 1 videocassette of 1 (U-matic): sd., col.; 3/4 in. (Box 34, Videotape 1)
    - John Sculley's address to South East Area meeting, 1988 June 13; 222; 1 videocassette of 1 (U-matic) (90 min.): sd., col.; 3/4 in. (Box 34, Videotape 2)
    - Nation's Business Today. Naisbitt & Co. Interview series with John Sculley and John Naisbitt, 1986 May 5-8; 22; 1 videocassette of 1 (U-matic): sd., col.; 3/4 in. (Box 34, Videotape 3)
    - Nation's Business Today. Naisbitt & Co. Excerpts from interview with John Sculley, [1986 May 5-8?]; 48; 1 videocassette of 1 (U-matic): sd., col.; 3/4 in. (Box 34, Videotape 4)
    - Pinnacle. Show no. 153. / CNN, 1987 Dec. 12; 188; 1 videocassette of 1 (U-matic) (30 min.): sd., col.; 3/4 in. (Box 34, Videotape 5)
      John Sculley, Chairman, Apple Computer
    - WSAA joke, 1986 Mar. 12; 125; 1 videocassette of 1 (U-matic) (7:30 min.): sd., col.; 3/4 in. (Box 34, Videotape 6)
    - John Sculley speeches [1 of 8]. Sculley - PCBA, 1980; 1 sound cassette (Box 92, Folder 41)
    - John Sculley speeches [2 of 8]. Sculley - Allegheny bottlers, 1980 Dec. 5; 1 sound cassette (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - John Sculley speeches [3 of 8]. PCBA Sculley, 1981 Dec. 4; 1 sound cassette (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - John Sculley speeches [4 of 8]. Address to Food Service sales force, undated; 1 sound cassette (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - John Sculley speeches [5 of 8]. Palm Springs Road show, 1982; 1 sound cassette (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - John Sculley speeches [6 of 8]. Untitled, undated; 1 sound cassette (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - John Sculley speeches [7 of 8]. Palm Springs Road show, 1981; 1 sound cassette (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - John Sculley speeches [8 of 8]. Boca Raton, 1981; 1 sound cassette (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - Corporate Briefing Center Videoconferences, Subseries 14.4
    This subseries includes videotapes of videoconferences coordinated through Apple's Corporate Briefing Center in Cupertino, California.
    - Corporate Briefing Center. Cimmaron Elementary computerized classroom, Cherry Creek Schools, 1986 July; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 31, Videotape 7)
    - Corporate Briefing Center videoconference, 1990 Jan. 19; 1 videocassette of 2 (c 1) (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 31, Videotape 8)
      Robert Wohnoutka - Appletalk
    - Corporate Briefing Center videoconference, 1990 Jan. 19; 1 videocassette of 2 (c 2) (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. + 1 computer diskette; 3.5 in. (Box 31, Videotape 9)
      IBM host Dave Nagy
    - Corporate Briefing Center videoconference: high volume CPU's, 1990 Mar. 16; 1 videocassette of 2 (c 1) (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 31, Videotape 10)
      Joe Harris & Brian Loucks
    - Corporate Briefing Center videoconference, 1990 Apr. 6; 1 videocassette of 2 (c 1) (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. + 1 computer diskette; 3.5 in. (Box 32, Videotape 1)
      Dave Nagy
    - Corporate Briefing Center videoconference, 1990 Apr. 6; 1 videocassette of 2 (c 2) (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 32, Videotape 2)
    - Corporate Briefing Center videoconference, 1990 Apr. 20; 1 videocassette of 2 (c 1) (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 32, Videotape 3)
      Hot water -- Karl May
    - Corporate Briefing Center videoconference, 1990 June 1; 1 videocassette of 2 (c 1) (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 32, Videotape 4)
      Steve Goldberg demoing System 7.0
    - Corporate Briefing Center videoconference, 1990 July 6; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 32, Videotape 5)
      Mac product strategy and direction update / Dan Simanek
    - Corporate Briefing Center videoconference, 1990 Nov. 2; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 32, Videotape 6)
      OASIS / Janine Firpo -- CPU S&D / Dan Simanek
    - Corporate Briefing Center videoconference, 1990 Dec. 7; 1 videocassette of 2 (c 1) (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 32, Videotape 7)
      Aruba/Peripherals / Dan Simanek
    - Briefing Center meeting #1, n.d. Aug 28; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 32, Videotape 8)
  - Chiat/Day Advertising videotapes, Subseries 14.5
    This subseries includes videotapes of various television commercials produced by Chiat/Day Advertising for Apple Computer. Includes some of the most memorable Apple commercials.
    - Chiat/Day Advertising. Apple computer show reel, 1983 Oct. 13; 82; 1 videocassette of 1 (Mini U-matic): sd., col.; 3/4 in. edited master (Box 35, Videotape 1)
      Best of Pepsi -- Alone again (0:30 min.) -- Breakfast (1 min.) -- Basketball (1 min.)
    - Chiat/Day Advertising. 1984, 1983 Dec. 9; 87; 1 videocassette of 1 (U-matic): sd., col.; 3/4 in. (Box 35, Videotape 2)
    - Chiat/Day Advertising. [Apple Computer advertizements], 1984 Oct. 23; 107; 1 videocassette of 1 (U-matic) (11 min.): sd., col.; 3/4 in. (Box 35, Videotape 3)
      Apple Macintosh -- Apple time capsule -- Apple Marcom
    - Chiat/Day Advertising. [Apple Computer advertizements], 1984 Nov.; 108; 1 videocassette of 1 (U-matic): sd., col.; 3/4 in. (Box 35, Videotape 4)
      Glove -- Unpack -- Chainsaw -- Sledgehammer
    - Chiat/Day Advertising. Lemmings, 1984 Dec. 20; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (1 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 35, Videotape 5)
    - Chiat/Day Advertising demo, 1986 May 9; 143; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 35, Videotape 6)
    - Chiat/Day Inc. Advertising. [Apple Computer advertizements], undated; 1 videocassette of 1 (U-matic): sd., col.; 3/4 in. (Box 35, Videotape 7)
      ApplePie -- Demo -- Detente -- Workgroup -- LaserWriter -- Vision -- Manuals/MO -- Ad infinitum/MO -- Major improvement -- Connections -- Software -- Do it yourself -- Understood (0:30 min.) -- Understoond (1 min.) -- Talk/software
    - Chiat/Day Inc. Advertising. [Apple Computer advertizements], undated; 115; 1 videocassette of 1 (U-matic): sd., col.; 3/4 in. (Box 36, Videotape 1)
      1984 -- Manuals -- Ad infinitum -- Gauntlet -- Building -- Factory (1 min.)
    - Chiat/Day Inc. Advertising. [Apple Computer advertizements], undated; 35; 1 videocassette of 1 (U-matic): sd., col.; 3/4 in. (Box 36, Videotape 2)
      Lemmings. Original v.o. -- Lemmings. Revised v.o.
    - Chiat/Day Inc. Advertising. Sedelmaier reel, undated; 29; 1 videocassette of 1 (U-matic): sd., col.; 3/4 in. (Box 36, Videotape 3)
    - Chiat/Day Inc. Advertising. Strictly business, undated; 28; 1 videocassette of 1 (U-matic): sd., col.; 3/4 in. (Box 36, Videotape 4)
    - Chiat/Day Inc. Advertising. Non-Apple ads, undated; 27; 1 videocassette of 1 (U-matic): sd., col.; 3/4 in. (Box 36, Videotape 5)
      Plank Road: Ice house -- California Cooler: Matt -- ORAL-B: Car -- Pizza Hut: Bedroom -- Nike: Michael Jordan/flying -- Apple Computer: Understood -- CBADD: The party's over
  - Apple TV videotapes, Subseries 14.6
    This subseries includes videotapes produced by Apple TV, Apple Computer's center responsible for internal video communications. Includes employee training videos, programs relating to various Apple-related projects worldwide, as well as videographies showing various ways in which Apple Computers have been used in governmental, educational, and corporate settings.
    - ATV: a new training tool, 1988 Dec. 7; AppleTV Broadcast no. 1; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (45 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 37, Videotape 1)
      Segment 1: Introduction to Apple TV -- Segment 2: Interview with Lee Klepinger and Mike Love -- Segment 3: Broadcast coordinating training tape
    - State of the market: market intelligence, 1988 Dec. 7; AppleTV Broadcast no. 2; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (37 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 37, Videotape 2)
      Segment 1: Comdex report with Jon Holtzman -- Segment 2: Presen[t]ation Manager analysis with Dave Garr -- Segment 3: Desktop Publishing benchmarks discussion with Mike Mace
    - K-12 curriculum - curriculum review, 1988 Dec. 9; AppleTV Broadcast no. 3; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (60 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 37, Videotape 3)
      Segment 1: Message to the field with Betsy Pace -- Segment 2: Market review with Marlene Teichert -- Segment 3: "Curriculum is" with Barbara Secrest Nelson -- Segment 4: Account executive viewpoint with Jack Powers -- Segment 5: Computers: a delivery method for instruction with Barbara Secrest Nelson -- Segment 6: Virginia: passport to literacy with Jackie Redmond -- Segment 7: "ESL" with Barbara Secrest Nelson -- Segment 8: Apple Learning Series with Dr. Michael Klencschy -- Segment 9: Apple Software Development with Paula McClain -- Segment 10: Conclusion
    - [Item not found at time of processing. Space reserved in case replacement can be obtained.], undated; AppleTV Broadcast no. 4 (Box 37, Videotape 4)
    - Live MACWORLD coverage, 1989 Jan. 20; AppleTV Broadcast no. 5; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (73 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 37, Videotape 5)
      John Sculley's keynote address with press conference highlights
    - K-12 Business of Education symposium telecast, 1989 Jan. 26; AppleTV Broadcast no. 6; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (53:30 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 37, Videotape 6)
      Segment 1: Introduction with Bernie Gifford -- Segment 2: Panel discussion reviewing issues facing school superintendents -- Segment 3: Competitive review with guest educator -- Segment 4: Success stories from the field related to superintendent's needs -- Segment 5: Making your time productive at the B.E.S. -- Segment 6: Q & A forum
    - Market intelligence update, 1989 Jan. 30; AppleTV Broadcast no. 7; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (53 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 37, Videotape 7)
    - Using Apple TV as a training tool, 1989 Jan. 31; AppleTV Broadcast no. 8; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (54 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 37, Videotape 8)
      Segment 1: Introduction to Apple TV -- Segment 2: Interview with Lee Klepinger, Michael Metz, Dennis Mahoney and Greg Shuk -- Segment 3: Q & A -- Segment 4: Open Apple special edition: MACWORLD (edited for broadcast)
    - Introduction to Macintosh fundamentals & beyond, 1989 Jan. 31; AppleTV Broadcast no. 9; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (42:30 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 37, Videotape 9)
      Segment 1: Demonstration of equipment set up of MacFab with James Laffey. Operations outline with Susan Kitchen -- Segment 2: Q & A session with Al Wong, Lee Klepinger, and James Laffey
    - Technical resources presents March technical update, 1989 Feb. 22; AppleTV Broadcast no. 10; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (120 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 37, Videotape 10)
      Segment 1: Interview with third party suppliers of 3270/5250 products for the Macintosh -- Segment 2: Review of MaWorkstation 3.1 -- Segment 3: Interview with third party developers -- Segment 4: Q & A session -- Segment 5: New product CPU announcement -- Segment 6: Q & A session
    - Spring products introduction, March '89: live from San Francisco, 1989 Mar. 7; AppleTV Broadcast no. 11; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (80 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 38, Videotape 1)
      Segment 1: Interview with Godfrey Sullivan -- Segment 2: Cobra presentation with Jean-Louis Gassee -- Segment 3: Cobra/Monitor configurations and the Macintosh Family Product Showcase with John Sculley -- Segment 4: Impact on the market areas with Larry Tesler -- Segment 5: Summary with Godfrey Sullivan
    - K-12 curriculum review financing educational technology, 1989 Mar. 17; AppleTV Broadcast no. 12; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (60 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 38, Videotape 2)
      Segment 1: Market update -- Segment 2: Business of education update: planning for April -- Segment 3: Federal funding and accessing federal dollars - "How to" and examples of successful programs -- Segment 4: Q & A session
    - New product training, March '89, 1989 Mar. 17; AppleTV Broadcast no. 13; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (30 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 38, Videotape 3)
      Segment 1: Apple II video overlay card introduction -- Segment 2: Overlay card set-up and installation -- Segment 3: Software demonstrations -- Segment 4: Educational use of the overlay card -- Segment 5: Q & A sessions
    - K-12 special education and rehabilitation solutions, 1989 Apr. 21; AppleTV Broadcast no. 14; 1 videocassette of 1 (VHS) (60 min.): sd., col.; 1/2 in. (Box 38, Videotape 4)
      Segment 1: K-12 market updates and Macintosh summer campaign -- Segment 2: Description of the special education marketplace -- Segment 3: Apple's special education sales tools -- Segment 4: Information on the National Special Education Alliance -- Segment 5: Future view of technology use by people with disabilities -- Segment 6: Q and A session